Narita's father hired his friend
to cause the accident and harm you.
"...caused by the father's friend"
Saneatsu Narita's Medical Records
He likely sacrificed your kidney
in return for a Prime Right.
Narita Saneatsu
is the key
Saneatsu Narita is the key to everything!
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
Dad was a member of the Camp...
The person who hit me was Dad's friend...
So Mom's death was just collateral damage.
I'm the key to Tasuketsu.
I can't stay with everyone else.
Ha! Quit kidding around.
I'm not kidding anyone.
I've done my best to survive and
defeat the Emperor with you guys,
but it turns out I was putting you
in harm's way for no good reason.
I don't deserve to be with you.
Are you serious?
You'll be fine without me.
You have Saaya.
You're our leader.
Saaya, we agreed that you—
I... I've always been scared of other people.
It's always just been me by myself, but...
Saneatsu, you called me a friend.
The only reason I'm able to talk with
everyone today is because of you, Saneatsu.
Omi...
I...
I'm only alive right now because of you!
'Cause you're the most important
person in the world to me!
Ryuta...
And I'm...
I'm no good at anything, but
you've always counted on me.
Kazuhiko...
When I was ready to give up,
Kazuhiko lit a fire in me.
But aren't you the one
who helped him do that, for real?
I'm still here because you showed me
the way when I wanted to run off.
You know...
Omi may be the one who saved my life,
but I believe in you as someone
Isshiki put her trust in.
Narita...
In my desperation to survive,
I became reckless.
But you and Sudo helped
someone as shallow as me.
I owe him my life, but you're the one
who shook some sense into him.
You're the man Ryohei Sudo trusted.
I almost feel bad for only
having one life I can owe you.
Saneatsu...
Even we were caught up in
simply making it out of Tasuketsu alive,
you were the first to decide
to defeat the Emperor.
Ever since that day, we've
been committed to that goal.
And that conviction gives me
strength every day.
Strength brought to me by your words.
We're here thanks to you.
You brought us together.
You're what holds us together.
So please, don't say that you'll leave.
You're already a part of us, Saneatsu.
You guys...
Thank—
Boom!
What's that for?!
If you've got time to cry,
then plan how we'll see Ren Iruga!
Come on, let's go!
Ryuta-kun really can't stand
a somber atmosphere...
Ren Iruga?
You know him, Souma?!
Yeah, from the Camp...
Ren Iruga came from the Camp. He's
the owner of the Prime Right of Division.
That's right!
I heard about someone who
pulled the strongest Prime Right.
Ren Iruga was supposedly their best friend.
I never heard that.
It was just a rumor among
a small group of people.
Researchers caught wind and
put it to bed pretty soon after...
Iruga was best friends with
the owner of the Obedience Right?
How can anyone
determine what's "strongest"
without knowing every
Right in the first place?
It'd be possible if you know
what's inside every envelope.
Exactly. The rumor was started
by the person who helped my dad...
the owner of the Prime Right
of Transillumination.
No one else could know the contents
of each envelope or see through rumors.
And if any rumors happened to be true,
they'd have to put an end to it.
So that's where Ren Iruga comes in.
He'd be the only clue to the
owner of the Obedience Right.
That's why the Camp kept
a close eye on Ren Iruga,
while also being careful
not to press him too hard.
Doesn't that sound like
the researcher is behind it all?
Right. That researcher is likely Mido.
This is way too hard for me to follow!
Fill me in on the conclusion later.
Change of plans!
Be it Iruga or Mido,
we'll lure one of them out.
Preferably Mido.
If my assumption is right, Mido's Prime Right
is something along the line of succession.
Even if it comes to armed conflict,
we have Ryuta and Souma.
But if Iruga or both of them show up,
let's try for a peaceful discussion.
If that's not possible, we'll retreat.
Sounds good.
His Prime Right is bad news.
How will we lure them out?
We'll need Gobo's help.
I'm thinking of drawing them here
using his Presentation Right.
So it's my time to shine
with these powers of mine,
banned at the Institution of Darkness...
Gobo?
Institution? Is he from the Camp too?
Very well. In times of need, leave it to—
That reminds me! Speaking of tonight!
Hey! I'm delivering my line here, for real!
What's happening tonight, Sensei?
We'll be able to narrow down the Emperor's
whereabouts from tonight's announcement!
What?!
The Emperor selects Designated
Areas out of the 23 wards.
As they mentioned at the
beginning of Tasuketsu.
According to Sudo, these areas
are determined by two principles.
Depending on the next area,
we can narrow it down
to one or two locations.
Are you sure?!
Take a look at this.
It's a map of the 23 wards.
If we mark the areas we've
passed through so far...
Suginami
Nakano
Nerima
Itabashi
Kita
It looks like this.
They're adjacent?
Exactly. Sudo concluded from our path so far
that we're moving in a clockwise
direction, spiraling inwards.
But some wards have
more than one adjacent ward.
Right. Suginami has Nerima and Nakano.
Suginami
Nakano
Nerima
Kita
Arakawa
Adachi
Kita, with Adachi and Arakawa.
Edogawa, with Sumida and Koto.
Edogawa
Sumida
Koto
Ota, with Meguro and Setagaya.
Ota
Meguro
Setagaya
Shinjuku, with Toshima and Bunkyo...
Shinjuku
Toshima
Bunkyo
and finally Bunkyo, with Arakawa and Taito.
Arakawa
Bunkyo
Taito
It's like there's one outwards
and one inwards.
Precisely.
Kita
Arakawa
Adachi
If Arakawa is announced tonight,
we'd be moving inwards.
And if it's Adachi, we'd head outwards.
We can determine the principle
depending on the outcome.
Adachi would signify a route
circling the outer wards.
But that poses two irregular areas.
Yeah. Nakano was an inner adjacent
ward, which we've already passed.
And it would leave out Meguro.
But if Arakawa were
to be announced tonight,
it would mean we'd go in order from in and out
when there are multiple adjacent wards,
just like we did from Suginami
to Nakano then Nerima.
That would include all 23 wards!
And the final destination
would become Chiyoda.
I never noticed any of this...
But how do we know the Emperor's there?
Because they're searching for whoever
is the key to defeating the Emperor.
If you trace the steps of the Camp's
researchers, it leads to Narita's accident.
That's how the Emperor learned of
a leaked "trump card" against them.
Their aim is to eliminate that trump card
by reaching its owner, Narita.
At least, that's what Sudo suspected.
So everything from the starting ward
to the area progression all lead to me?
That's right.
They assumed only the owner of the trump card
could determine why it started in Suginami.
The Emperor, Tasuketsu, and Rights...
Very few people likely realize
the connection between the three.
Hang on. Why go about it
in such a roundabout way?
The owner of the Obedience Right died, right?
Which means the Emperor recovered it.
Why not just use the Obedience Right
to force Saneatsu to meet them?
Of course. That's because...
There's a chance the owner of
the Obedience Right is still alive.
Alive?!
I'm just saying, there's a chance.
But if they are, can't they
defeat the Emperor?
Or even if they're on the Emperor's
side, why aren't they using it?
You're right.
Based on what's happened so far,
it looks like the Emperor's only method
to kill us is through Tasuketsu.
Or maybe they can't use the
Obedience Right for whatever reason.
The answer to that is probably easiest
to find out from Iruga or Mido.
Okay, so what am I supposed to display?
It's almost today's tally time.
Not that there'll be a tally...
Right...
In case it's useful information,
we still have electricity,
water, and radio waves.
Meaning it's likely the Emperor
needs them too.
Radio waves to conduct Tasuketsu.
Water for obvious reasons.
What's a mystery is electricity.
Ya, he can display Tasuketsu without it.
And it's not necessarily
a lifeline, either.
Could it be for a security system?
Interesting. So the Emperor
is in a safe location.
Then we might be able to catch him
off guard if we turn off the power!
I'm already on it.
The majority of Tokyo's power is generated
at the Shinagawa Thermal Power Station
and the Oi Thermal Power Station.
Even if the Emperor has
an in-house power generator,
a surprise attack on the two power
stations could temporarily cut supply.
This would shut down their security
system, creating a brief opening.
Tonight's announcement should
reveal the Emperor's location
for us to formulate a complete plan.
So we'll raid the power stations, cause
a blackout, and head to the Emperor...
Okay, so here's the message!
Kanagawa's farther than
I thought, Teppei-chan.
It's time. We will not be taking tally.
Would you look at that.
Someone did good work.
Calling all survivors.
We are the Resistance, in search
of comrades to defeat the Emperor.
We have a path to victory depending
on reinforcement.
Meet us tomorrow at noon inside the
City Hall of the Designated Area.
If you do not wish to aid us, stay away.
Those identified as threats will be eliminated.
Cool. A resistance, huh?
Sounds like a fun little event!
We have a path to victory depending
on reinforcement.
Meet us tomorrow at noon inside the
City Hall of the Designated Area.
If you do not wish to aid us, stay away.
Those identified as threats will be eliminated.
Tomorrow at noon... Too bad I can't make it.
Hmm... I'd say they're really closing in.
Now, for the announcement
of tomorrow's Designated Area.
Tomorrow's area is...
Arakawa Ward
Arakawa.
The Emperor's location is... Chiyoda!
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
Look at this room. It's spotless!
Just what you'd expect from
that overly sincere Teppei-chan.
I wonder if I'd change my mind
if he were still alive...
I don't care what Prime Right
I have. I'll never use it!
It'd basically be approving
what they've done.
I'll expose their evils the right way!
Justice will win, no matter what!
I guess you were wrong, Teppei-chan.
I wouldn't think everything was futile
if justice won in this world.
Justice, value... All of it
is decided by the majority.
It's nonsense―a mountain of prejudice
disguised as the "right answer."
I get it now that you've died, Teppei-chan.
There really was no such thing as justice.
Teppei-chan's cell phone?
He always kept it on him...
So I guess this is where he died.
But... something's not making sense.
The Emperor hasn't used the Obedience Right,
so it's natural to assume they
haven't been able to recover it.
Which got my hopes up that
Teppei-chan might still be alive.
After all, I'm the only one
who knew where he lived.
I actually thought we'd make it if we
could just beat Mido to the punch.
One New Voice Memo
I'm Teppei Yoshii.
I'm leaving this message in case
something happens to me.
Teppei-chan's voice...
This message is for Ren...
my best friend Ren Iruga.
Ren, I know you'll find
this message, no matter what.
The only person stupid enough
to trust me is you, Teppei-chan.
Look inside "my favorite thing."
You'll find numbers marked.
Start from one.
If something happens to me,
I hope it's enough.
So that's what's going on.
I get it now, Teppei-chan...
You loved music, which means...
There we go.
Adhered parts of the stereo... divide.
You'll find numbers marked. Start from one.
For Ren,
Even if I die, as long as
this first envelope is safe,
the Obedience Right will belong to me.
Envelopes two through five each
contain a simple command.
They'll only work once against
the first person who sees them.
How they should be used is something
I'll leave for you to decide.
I believe in you to finish the rest...
since you're my best friend.
The commands written in
envelopes two through five are...
Can you imagine if someone
other than me found these?!
All this work without your eyesight...
Did you even consider someone
using this for their own benefit?
Teppei-chan, you're a bit of a dope
for someone so sincere.
Although, I didn't mind that about you...
Thanks to you, I may just
change my mind about the world.
Let's see...
Mido's definitely out of the question.
But I dunno if I'm cut out for it, either...
I'll defeat the Emperor
and put an end to Tasuketsu!
Oh, right...
He'd be perfect for the job.
Teppei-chan's only keepsake...
I won't let anyone near it.
I'll keep it safe as long as I live.
Now, let's go pass down
Teppei-chan's justice.
Arakawa City Hall
Are you guys the ones who sent that message?
That's right.
Damn it! They're just a bunch of kids!
Just to be safe... You aren't
the Emperor, are you?
Nuh-uh! Why'd you ask?
How were you able to send that message then?
With my Right... the Presentation Right!
We found a way to defeat the Emperor,
so we're looking for reinforcements.
Defeat the Emperor?!
I-Is that true?!
C'mon, don't believe them! Remember...
We came here desperate with the
hope of defeating the Emperor.
We risked our lives to get here!
And this is what we get?!
A bunch of kids?!
Y-You're right... There's no way
we can take your word!
Hang on a sec... What if these guys
are the Emperor's pawns?!
Well?!
Answer us!
You all! Straighten up and be quiet!
H-Hey... Why am I...
My body... won't listen...
The strongest Prime Right
of Obedience... belongs to me!
The Obedience Right?
Wha—?!
My Prime Right is the
Physical Manipulation Right.
If I wanted to kill ya,
I'd have already done it.
We've got chops and a plan.
All we need is a bigger headcount.
Which is why we called
for gutsy people like you guys.
I hope you'll trust us and lend us your help.
But if you can't, go ahead and leave.
Fine, I trust you.
It's the only hand we've got.
Yeah! With your powers, I'm sure
we can defeat the Emperor!
So, what exactly is this plan of yours?
We'd ask you guys
to take on the safest roles.
Safest?
Ones that don't require any Rights.
Huh...
Also, we need an Assistant Officer.
Assistant Officer?!
Any volunteers?
I'll do it.
I'd be happy to—actually...
I demand to.
Perfect. It's decided, then.
You four can climb to
the rooftop and wait there.
Huh?
Hey! What's that about?!
Don't worry. This building's safe.
Our comrades that can
spot enemies are on guard.
Well, well... what a bold strategy.
It was worth dragging
my feet here, after all.
Shut up while you walk... Mido!
Nice to meet you,
Sanetomo Narita's
dear son...
Pass Down